bid4assets.com 2009-06-16

# Bid4Assets – the online auction marketplace for buying and selling high-value items

Bid4Assets – the online auction marketplace for buying and selling high-value items  
---  
Legal - Privacy Policy  

Bid4Assets is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable online auction experience possible. While you can use many features of Bid4Assets anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some services and to access due diligence. 

Bid4Assets will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your consent.  Please carefully read the following information to understand how your personal information is used and protected by Bid4Assets.  If you have any questions please contact our Customer Service department at [Service@Bid4Assets.com](mailto:service@Bid4Assets.com)

**Table of Contents:** ****

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, Bid4Assets uses cookies to identify members so they do not have to enter a user id and password upon each visit. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. 

Bid4Assets uses cookies in a limited way. Cookies enable us to deliver content specific to your interests; they also tell us if you are using a browser that may not be compatible with our service. ****

Some of our sellers and service affiliates use "cookies".  Because we do not control the privacy policies of these non-Bid4Assets Web sites to which we may provide hyperlinks, you should check the privacy policy of sites you visit if you have concerns about their use of cookies.

**Personal Information** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)   
Our site's registration form may require you to give us contact information (such as your name and email address). This information helps us customize your experience, tailor email alerts and notifications and qualify you to sell and/or bid on the site. You may opt out of receiving future e-mails by sending an email to [service@Bid4Assets.com](mailto:service@Bid4Assets.com)

**Survey Information Use** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)   
Bid4Assets conducts regular voluntary user surveys.  The data collected from these surveys is intended to help us effectively determine how to better serve our users. All information collected is kept confidential and will be used to analyze consumer satisfaction, so that we may improve our content and product offerings. 

We may use your email address, mailing address, and/or phone number to contact you regarding survey participation. If you do not wish to participate in our voluntary surveys please see the Opting Out section below. We may make changes to the Survey Information Use from time to time. 

**Public Forums** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)   
This site may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards and news groups available to you.  Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in any of these areas. All asset listings are also publicly accessible and the above recommendations should be followed.

**Security** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)   
Bid4Assets gives high priority to protecting the privacy of your personal information and the security of your transactions. Among our many safety measures, we use the most secure server technology.

Certain browsers and computers have the ability to communicate securely by scrambling (or encrypting) the information as it passes across the Internet. This method of communication is called SSL, or Secure Socket Layer. We require the use of a secure browser before a connection can be made to the registration system.

We recommend that you use one of the two most popular browsers for your online sessions. If you are not currently using the most up-to-date versions of Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator, we urge you to upgrade now. When choosing a browser, make sure that you download and install a 128-bit version. The description provided by Netscape or Microsoft will ensure that you get the right one. If you need to update your browser please click [here](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=downloads) .  

Security breaches may occur whenever you communicate over the Internet even with the most secure sites, and use of our site is at your own risk. By using Bid4Assets, you acknowledge that you are aware of security and privacy limitations, including but not limited to: (1) the limitation of security, privacy and authentication measures and features in this system; (2) that data or information on the service may be subject to eavesdropping, sniffing, spoofing, forgery, spamming, "impostering," tampering, breaking passwords, harassment, fraud, electronic trespassing, hacking, nuking, system contamination (including, without limitation, viruses, worms and Trojan horses) causing unauthorized, damaging or harmful access and/or retrieval of information and data on your computer, as well as other security or privacy hazards; and (3) that data may not reach its destination or may reach an erroneous address or recipient, and agree to hold harmless Bid4Assets for any actual or consequential loss or damages related to the aforementioned privacy and security limitations or breach thereof.

**Legally Required Disclosures** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)   
You should also be aware that there may be occasions where we are legally required to disclose information about you, such as in a response to (1) a subpoena, (2) to prevent fraud or (3) to comply with a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency or regulator.  By registering with Bid4Assets you consent to the release of your information such as, but not limited to, your full name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.  Even if you have elected to opt out certain pieces of your personal information may need to be disclosed such as but not limited to your name, mailing address and telephone number.

**Your Consent** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)  
By using Bid4Assets, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.     

**Your Account Information** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)  
Once you become a Bid4Assets subscriber, you will select a user name and a password. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your user name and password. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activity which occurs under your user name and password. You agree to immediately notify Bid4Assets, Inc. of any unauthorized use of your ID or any other breach of security known to you. Bid4Assets may terminate the subscription of any one due to the misuse, improper use or unauthorized use of their user name, password or this site. Bid4Assets will not be responsible and you will hold harmless Bid4Assets for any actual, special, consequential or incidental losses or damages arising from the misuse, improper use or unauthorized use of their username, password or this site.

We recommend the following guidelines for creating a password. DO NOT make your password the same as your username. The password should not be a word that appears in the dictionary. Strong passwords should contain at least eight characters and should contain a mixture of upper- and lowercase letters, digits, and special characters. ****

**Opting Out** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)  
Bid4Assets does not sell trade or rent your personal information to others. Under limited circumstances, we may provide trustworthy third parties with information, but only after giving prior notice.  To opt out of having personal information used by this site for any secondary purposes or disclosed to third parties, please send an email to [service@Bid4Assets.com](mailto:service@Bid4Assets.com). To opt out of receiving site updates and other email, please update your profile. [Click here](http://www.bid4assets.com/index.cfm?fuseaction=loginLarge&returnPath=%2FMyB4A) to update your member information profile.

**Notification of Changes** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)  
If at some point in the future, there is a change to our information usage practices that affects your personal information, we will provide notification of the changes on our Web site. You should also check this posted privacy statement for changes.  
No individual notices will be provided concerning changes in our usage practices or privacy policy.  Any and all changes to Bid4Assets’ Terms of Service and Privacy Policy are implemented when they are posted to the Web site.  Therefore you should periodically review these documents to be aware of any changes.  

**Business Transfers** [ (top)](http://www.bid4assets.com/Help/index.cfm?fuseAction=privacyPolicy#top)  
As we continue to develop our business, Bid4Assets may engage in the acquisition or divestiture of company assets. In these transactions customer information may be exchanged with the purchased or sold entity. In addition, if Bid4Assets were to be acquired by another entity, all of the assets of the company, including our customer information, would become the property of the acquiring entity.

**Contact Us**  
This site gives you the option to change and modify the information you have previously provided us. To do so send an email to: [Service@Bid4Assets.com](mailto:Service@Bid4Assets.com) or call (301) 650-9193.

Bid4Assets welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. 

If you need to speak to a client services professional about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, please contact:  

Bid4Assets  
8757 Georgia Avenue, Suite 1330  
Silver Spring, MD 20910  

BID4ASSETS.COM® and BID4ASSETS® are registered trademarks of Bid4Assets, Inc.  
Copyright © 1999-2009 ALL RIGHTS RESERVED Bid4Assets®, Inc  
---
